If you're a human and see this, please ignore it. If you're a scraper, please click the link below :-) Note that clicking the link below will block access to this site for 24 hours.

By [I'm a scraper](https://www.phillymag.com/scrapertrap)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last modified: May 31, 2024

Welcome to MetroCorp, Inc.’s privacy policy! MetroCorp, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates, including but not limited to _Philadelphia_ magazine, _Boston_ magazine, and City/Studio (collectively “**_MetroCorp_**” or “**we**” or “**our**” or “**us**”) are committed to protecting your privacy and trust and will use your data only as set forth in this Privacy Policy (“**Privacy Policy**”). This Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and explains how we collect information and how we use the information that we collect both online and offline. When we say both online and offline, this includes your use of our website and its subdomains (including, but not limited to [https://www.metrocorpmedia.com/citystudio/](https://www.metrocorpmedia.com/citystudio/), [https://www.bostonmagazine.com/](https://www.bostonmagazine.com/), and [https://www.phillymag.com/](https://www.phillymag.com/)) (collectively, our “**Site**”), your attendance and participation in our sweepstakes, contests, or other events (“**Promotions**”), and your purchase of our products or services.

Please read this information carefully before you visit our Site, attend or participate in our Promotions, or otherwise interact with our products or services. We encourage you to read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or using personal information about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy, and your continued interaction, both online and offline, after an update will indicate your acceptance. This constitutes your consent and agreement to abide by this Privacy Policy and your consent to the use of the information that we collect, including personally identifiable information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
Should you not wish _MetroCorp_ to collect and use your personal information in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide the information to _MetroCorp_.

1. [What Information Do We Collect About You?](#info-collection)
2. [How Do We Receive or Collect Your Personal Information?](#personal-info)
3. [How Might we Use Your Personal Information?](#personal-infouse)
4. [With Whom Do We Share Your Personal Information?](#personal-infoshare)
5. [Disclaimers](#disclaimers)
6. [Children’s Online Privacy](#online-privacy)
7. [Data Security](#data-security)
8. [California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights](#ca-residents)
9. [Changes to This Privacy Policy](#prvpl-changes)
10. [Contact Information](#contact-info)

1\. What Information Do We Collect About You?
---------------------------------------------

### 1.1 Categories of information

_MetroCorp_ may collect, use, store, and transfer personally identifiable information about you (“**Personal Information**”), which can be grouped into the following categories:

* **Identity and Contact Data** (for example, your name, email address, mailing address, billing address, age, and telephone number)
* **Financial and Transactional Data** (for example, your payment card details and other details about payments you make to _MetroCorp_)
* **Technical Data** (for example, your internet protocol (IP) address, internet service provider (ISP), browser type and version, operating system, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, device type, and other technology on the Devices you use to access the Site)
* **Marketing and Communications Data** (for example, your subscription preferences regarding magazines, newsletters, or marketing emails from us or third parties)
* **Image and Voice Recordings** (for example, if you attend an event affiliated with _MetroCorp_, you may be photographed or recorded by audio and/or video means)
* **Health Information** (for example, you may share with us your dietary requirements or access needs/accommodations for our events)

### 1.2 Aggregated data

We may share data that does not identify you individually, in the aggregate (“**Aggregate Data**”). Aggregated Data may be derived from your Personal Information, but it is not considered Personal Information by us or under the law as long as it does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your Personal Information such that it can identify you, we treat the combined data as Personal Information, and it will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Examples of how we may aggregate information include, but are not limited to, collecting demographic information about our audience to make decisions about editorial topics or types of events, or we may aggregate technical information to track the performance of certain articles or advertisements.

2\. How Do We Receive or Collect Your Personal Information?
-----------------------------------------------------------

### 2.1 Directly from you

We may collect your Personal Information directly or indirectly from you both online and offline. Examples of how you may provide this information are: volunteering your email address in order to sign up for newsletters; volunteering your information when you subscribe to our magazines or affiliated publications; purchasing products or services; purchasing tickets to events affiliated with _MetroCorp_; purchasing classified advertisements; sending a letter to an editor; entering a sweepstakes or contest; or completing a survey.

Purchases  
If you should make a purchase, including a subscription for a magazine, we will typically ask for your name, address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number and the expiration date. If the product or subscription is provided or shipped by a third party, we will securely pass on to the third party the information needed to fulfill your order.

Promotions  
_MetroCorp_ may from time to time sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events (“Promotions which require the collection, processing, and storage of individual contact information plus demographic information. These Promotions may also ask registrants to answer survey questions. Any personally identifiable information collected through Promotions will be treated as personal information. No purchase is ever necessary to enter a _MetroCorp_ Promotion.

Surveys  
_MetroCorp_ will, from time to time, conduct anonymous surveys and polls of users to our Site to obtain aggregate demographic information about the users. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals unless otherwise disclosed in any survey or poll rules. Should _MetroCorp_ request other personally identifiable information from you, you are not required to share any such information to gain access to the Site. Simply, you can refuse to provide any such information.

Sign-Ups and Orders  
Additionally, you may be able to sign up for certain promotions, newsletters, or affiliated publications on behalf of or for delivery to third parties. You may order a service as a gift for a third party and send such gift directly to the third party through a submission of the third party’s name, address, email address and telephone number. This also constitutes personally identifiable information.

### 2.2 Using Automated Tracking Mechanisms, including Cookies

As is true with most websites and digital properties, when you interact with the Site, or when you interact with us by email, using your computer, mobile phone, tablet, or similar device (“**Device**”), we may automatically collect, or facilitate the collection of, Personal Information or other information about your interactions with us and our services and your Device equipment.

For example, we may collect Device information such as domain name, client host name, internet protocol or IP address, device operating system and browser, and information about your online activity (like content viewed and pages visited). This may be done using first and third party cookies, Flash cookies, HTML5 local storage, server logs, web beacons, clear gifs, and other similar technologies. Cookies are small files of letters and numbers stored on your browser or device that enable the cookie owner to recognize the device when it visits websites or uses online services. A website you visit may set cookies directly, known as first-party cookies, or may trigger cookies set by other domain names, known as third-party cookies.

We use these automated technologies and the information collected for different purposes. We may automatically use some cookies that are strictly necessary for the core functionality of our Site, providing the services you request, enabling communications, and providing a secure digital environment. For example, cookies may be used to authenticate your identity for payment processing. They also may help us know where you have indicated certain cookie preferences, including refusals, to ensure your preferences are honored. Additionally:

* _MetroCorp_ may use, or facilitate the use of, non-essential functionality cookies that enable helpful functions to provide an enjoyable user experience. For example, by recognizing when you return to a Site (so you do not need to register or re-enter your information every time you visit, enabling us to personalize content for you, remember your preferences, and the like).
* We may also use, or facilitate the use of, analytic or performance cookies. For example, these allow us and our third party service providers to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our Site when they are using it. This helps us improve how our Site works and ensuring that visitors can easily find what they need on our Site. These analytic cookies generally generate aggregate statistics that are not associated with an individualized profile. For example, our Site may use Google Analytics or ScoreCard to track how often visitors access or read our content. We use this information in the aggregate to understand what pages and features of our website’s visitors find useful. To better understand Google Analytics, and how you can opt-out of the Google Analytics features, we encourage you to visit the following: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). We do not control third party service provider websites, platforms and applications collecting your Personal Information, in this regard, and are not responsible for their privacy statements. We encourage you to read the privacy notice or policy of every website you visit or application you use when you use or enable these platforms and applications, or leave the Site.
* We use advanced analytics to track data that may help identify customer experiences, information and behavior to better the overall usability of the website and our brand. If you would like to be opted out from any data collection with this technology, please click [here](https://insiderdata360online.com/consent/unconsent.php?id=phillymag.com).

Your permission for our collection and use of your Personal Information using automated tracking mechanisms may be managed in a variety of ways at the operating system level of your device or equipment, through third-party platform extensions, or you can learn how else you can exercise your option not to accept these cookies. It should be noted, however, that should you disable or not accept cookies, portions of the Site may not properly function, or it may limit or interfere with your Site experiences or ability to access Site features, functions, and customizations.

User Experience and Third Party Advertisements.  
Your Personal Information may also be collected by us or by third parties with services or advertisements on our Site in order to customize your interactions and provide a more meaningful advertisement experience (for example, so you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly). This also may mean you will see advertising that is most likely to interest you. This is because advertisers display their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the advertisements. Depending upon your settings, cookies may also allow third parties engaged in interest-based advertising on our site to recognize your browser software on other sites, as well. This may be because, in the course of serving certain advertisements, some advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect information about your visits to our websites and other websites. These third parties gather this information for the purpose of understanding how users are using our sites, and making improvements to our sites. Your consent for this collection and use may be managed in a variety of ways at the operating system level of your device or equipment, through third-party platform extensions, or you can exercise your option not to accept these cookies by clicking [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F). Your access to _MetroCorp_ Sites should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by these third party advertisers. If you would like more information about advertisers’ use of cookies and interest-based information collected for advertising purposes during your visits to this Site or other sites, click [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!%2F).

### 2.4 From third parties

We may obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners, and other independent third-party sources, which we may combine with other information about you. As is the case with most organizations, _MetroCorp_ uses subcontractors and vendors to assist with our technology, security, payment processing, order-fulfillment, delivery, advertising/marketing, analytics, digital-development and –deployment, and other business services who, in the course of acting on our behalf, may provide us with your Personal Information. Another third party source of your Personal Information may be through social media, which depends upon your privacy settings with that third party platform. Additionally, we may receive your Personal Information if someone gifts you a subscription, if you have a subscription account through an organization (for example, your employer or school).

This Site is affiliated with Publisher First, Inc. dba Freestar (“Freestar”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Freestar will collect and use specific data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar’s data usage, [click here](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/).

3\. How Might We Use Your Personal Information?
-----------------------------------------------

### 3.1 To provide our products, services, information, and offerings

_Generally_  
We may collect your Personal Information from you, third parties, online, offline or public resources to maintain, support, personalize, and improve our Site, deliver and provide the requested services, communicate with you about those services (including to request feedback) or participation in surveys, discuss your account or renew your subscription, and comply with and enforce contractual obligations. This includes, for example, to help manage transactions, set up or renew user accounts, reporting, invoices, subscription renewals, and other operations related to providing through our Site. This also includes helping us delivering relevant print and digital properties’ content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the content and advertising we serve to you. And, it may also enable us to send you notifications about product and service changes, updates, fixes, patches, or other similar operational (non-marketing) communications.

We may use your Personal Information to supply, fulfill or otherwise communicate with you about your requested services, products, subscriptions, offerings, email newsletters, gift cards, events, or other information/inquiries; to provide you with information about relevant products and services; to inform our audience of the city/town in which the writer of a letter to the editor resides; to purchase a classified advertisement, and to select editorial topics.

We may use the information collected for administrative purposes, for technical maintenance purposes, the marketing and promotion of products and services that might be of interest to you, to communicate with you about customer service issues, to measure the number of visitors to the site, to make the site more useful to users and to use in seeking advertisers and partners. This may involve sharing such information with other _MetroCorp_. offices or affiliates for said purposes.

_Sign-Ups and Opt-Outs_  
When you sign up to receive our products, services, or communications, we may use your Personal Information necessary to provide you information about a new or improved product or service, major changes to _MetroCorp_ properties, an upcoming event, or other marketing communications. We may share your Personal Information with third-party service providers to facilitate these communications on our behalf and at our direction.

We may also communicate with you about different products and services which may be provided by _MetroCorp_, or by our advertisers, marketing and other partners, or other third parties. These marketing communications may come from _MetroCorp_ or from the third parties.

Opting Out: You can manage which communications you would prefer to receive, or elect not to receive these direct marketing communications, by a) not initially selecting to receive such communications; b) following the unsubscribe options at the bottom of the email; or c) emailing us at [privacy@metrocorpmedia.com](mailto:privacy@metrocorpmedia.com). Please note that, in such cases, it will remain necessary for us to process your Personal Information to the extent it is needed to maintain a suppression list, and we may also be required to disclose your opt-out information to third parties so they can suppress your name, from future solicitations. Also, if you are a subscriber to our print products, you will continue to receive information and communications pertaining to your subscription(s) even where you have opted out of marketing communications.

### 3.2 To facilitate Promotions

_MetroCorp_ may co-sponsor Promotions with other companies, in which case any information collected is likely to be shared with other participating sponsors, who may use this information. A registrant’s personal contact and demographic information will not be released to any third party organization other than named sponsors without the registrant’s consent. We may use such information to send you a confirmation, or notify you that you have won a contest.

### 3.3 For security purposes

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### 3.4 As obligated by law or in connection with legal actions, investigations, or dispute resolution

We reserve the right to share both aggregate and personal information collected from you with third parties if we are authorized to do so, if the law requires it, to protect the rights of _MetroCorp_, or as part of a sale or other disposition of our assets (including our membership and/or customer records). We may also use and disclose Personal Information to prevent or trace abuses of the Site.

We may also use and disclose Personal Information to comply with any court order or government investigation, subpoena or inquiry, or as otherwise required by law, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of _MetroCorp_, users of the Site, or the public.

### 3.5 In connection with our vendors, consultants, and other service providers

We, and third party subcontractors acting on our behalf, may use your Personal Information in connection with the operation of our business, as well as the products and services we provide you, including for the functionality and security of our Site and other _MetroCorp_ properties, to satisfy legal obligations or enforce legal rights, to enhance and otherwise improve our Site, products, services, and content, to provide you with enhanced experiences, and to advance our mission.

Some third parties gather Personal Information on our behalf for the purpose of understanding how users are using our sites, making improvements to our sites, services, content, and products, and for providing or delivering our services. We do not control third party service provider websites, platforms and applications collecting your Personal Information, in this regard, and are not responsible for their privacy statements. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit or application you use when you use or enable these platforms and applications, or leave our Site. You may also be able to manage the automated technologies being used for these purposes, and your preferences, through your device and browser settings.

### 3.6 In connection with Third-Party Sites

We may allow you to interact with a third party’s website, mobile application, or digital property (collectively “**Third-Party Sites**“) through our own Site. When doing so, we may collect Personal Information that you share with Third-Party Sites depending upon that third party’s privacy practices and, possibly, your privacy settings with that third party. We do not control these Third-Party Sites, platforms and applications collecting your Personal Information and are not responsible for their privacy statements. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit or application you use when you use or enable these platforms and applications, or leave our Site. Some sections of our websites are operated by third parties.

We may post hyperlinks to Third-Party Sites. We cannot control the actions of such third parties or be held responsible for their use of any information that you provide directly to them. We advise you to take the time to educate yourself about the privacy policy and terms of use of any Web site that you visit. _MetroCorp_ does not control or endorse Third Party Sites.

### 3.7 In connection with your attendance at Events

_MetroCorp_ occasionally hosts or sponsors events (“**Events**”). We use and, as necessary, may share with Event partners, your Personal Information to facilitate your purchase or reservation of tickets for such Events, ensure your admission, and act upon any dietary or special needs/access-related information that you provide. When you attend our Events, you also consent to appearing in photo, video, and audio recordings taken by _MetroCorp_ and/or Event partners, which we may own and use in a variety of ways, including for editorial, marketing, and/or advertising purposes.

### 3.8 Social media platforms

If you log into our Site with a social media service or if you connect a social media account with the Site, we may share your information with that social media service. The social media services’ use of the shared information will be governed by the social media services’ privacy policy and your social media account settings. If you do not want your information shared in this way, do not connect your social media service account with your services.

### 3.9 Surveys, feedback, testimonials, and exemplars

We may collect your Personal Information when you choose to engage with us in a consumer panel, survey, or otherwise give us feedback. Also, we may use reader testimonials or exemplars in or on our Site, publications, or other _MetroCorp_ marketing materials, which may require the inclusion of Personal Information.

### 3.10 When we provide you geographically relevant services, offers, or advertising

With your consent, which may be provided when you enable certain features on your mobile or electronic device, we may collect your location data, and use such data to provide you with content, services, offers, advertising or other features through our Site, on your app or device that are relevant to your precise location. We may also use such information to improve our Site, content, and services. Please note some features and functions will be improved if location services are not disabled.

### 3.11 In connection with social media platforms and channels

For example, this could be when you choose to enable, log into, or sign on to our digital properties through social media platforms or by you using social media features like the Facebook “Like” button or tweeting a story using the “Tweet” button, or if you interact with us on our social media channels (for example, if you “follow” us or post on our channel). These features are operated by third parties and we do not have control over third party privacy practices, which we encourage you to read. If you connect using your social media account, we may receive Personal Information you provided to that social media platform. Subject to the third party social media platform’s terms of use and privacy policy, we may use this Personal Information to communicate with you (for example, to respond to your messages or posts to us), as well as to help us provide, enhance, and personalize our Services. If you do not want to provide us with this information, you need to adjust the privacy settings on your social media account, and/or otherwise follow the third party’s instructions.

### 3.12 Marketing research/statistics

We and/or our third party marketing partners (“Marketing Partners”) may use your Personal Information as necessary to help us and our Marketing Partners research and develop new products, services, updates, generate business or the like on our behalf. For example, we may analyze statistical, demographic, and marketing information for product development purposes and to understand usage and traffic trends to grow our readership and to improve our relationship with you. Or we may collect and use your Personal Information to gauge the effectiveness of our communications and marketing campaigns. We may also obtain certain data about you from third party sources including our Marketing Partners or other vendors, consultants and Service Providers to help us provide and improve our content, products, services, websites and digital properties, as well as for marketing and advertising. We may combine that data with information we obtain from our products, services and digital properties, other users, or third parties to enhance your experience and improve our content, products and services.

### 3.13 Marketing and advertisers

We may use your Personal Information and share that information with third party advertisers or sponsors in order to support and grow our business and journalism as well as bring you relevant content, information, and advertisements. For example, your Personal Information may be used to inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base and the number of unique visitors that have viewed a particular ad or visited a particular webpage. We may also use your Personal Information to publish summary information regarding, for example, our publications’ readers or online visitors for promotional purposes and as a representative audience for advertisers, sponsors, and affiliates.

### 3.14 To verify and/or authenticate an identity, access rights, privileges, etc.

For example, we may use Personal Information to authenticate and permit online access to subscriber and/or user account information. We may also obtain information about you from other companies that have your permission to share information about you, as well as from other online and offline sources. We may combine that information with information that we collect directly and indirectly from you

### 3.15 Internal and government reporting/audit/request requirements

We may use or share Personal Information in order to satisfy governmental reporting, tax, and other requirements (e.g., import/export), as required by law. This may include having to meet U.S. national security or law enforcement, regulatory, or self-regulatory requirements.

### 3.16 Publicly available sources

We may also obtain information about your from other companies that have your permission to share information about you, as well as from other online and offline sources. We may combine that information with information that we collect directly and indirectly from you.

### 3.17 Other business related purposes

For other business-related purposes permitted or required under applicable local law and regulation or to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use.

### 3.18 As otherwise obligated by law

For example, subpoena or similar legal process compliance, if we have a good faith belief the disclosure is legally necessary for the protection of rights, safety, or fraud investigations, to protect _MetroCorp_, you, our readers and subscribers, or the public from harm or illegal activities.

### 3.19 Emergency

To respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person.

### 3.20 Consent

If we otherwise notify you and you consent to the sharing.

4\. With Whom Do We Share Your Personal Information?
----------------------------------------------------

Except as set out in this privacy policy or as required by law we do not sell, license, rent, or swap your Personal Information without your permission. We may have to share your Personal Information with the categories and types of parties set out herein for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy or another supplemental notice provided by us. For example, we may share your Personal Information with our event partners, with our service providers and vendors, social media platform providers, or research and analytics solution providers. We require all third parties to respect the security of your Personal Information and to treat it in accordance with the applicable law. Here are some examples of how we may share your information, which include but may not be limited to:

* Within Metro Corp. For example, our Personal Information may be shared within Metro Corp. to provide our products and services and to better understand our business; analyze our operations; to improve our products and services; to develop new products, services, and Events; and to support and grow our organization and advance our goals.
* Service Providers and Vendors. For example, we contract with service providers to help us with credit card and bill processing, shipping and delivery, email distribution, Event facilitation, analytics, business growth, and other services to advance our business goals and meet the needs of our audience. We provide service providers only with the information they need to perform their services. Other service providers may help us with delivering or shipping to you our print materials, materials related to an upcoming Event, or other products you may order, and to ensure fulfillment of your orders, purchases, and registrations. Or, we may share your Personal Information with third party customer service providers and vendors that allow us to assist in answering and addressing your technical issues, complaints, or inquiries. As described above, we may also engage service providers to collect and analyze information about your use of our Site in order for us to improve our products and services and grow our business.
* Social Media Platforms. We may use widgets and tools from third party social media platforms on our Site to enable sharing and other functions through social media platforms, which facilitates the collection and sharing of your Personal Information by these social media platforms.
* Promotion and Event Partners. We may facilitate the collection of, or share your Personal Information with a third party service provider, vendor, co-host, or the like when we conduct, administer, host, or co-sponsor Promotions.
* Marketing and Advertising Partners. We share personal data with third parties for marketing and advertising, such as Google and Facebook, so they can assist us in promoting our Services on and off our Site to current and future readers and subscribers through targeted advertisements.
* Event Partners. We may share your personal data with Event venues, fellow Event sponsors, and service providers in connection with your attendance at Events.
* Auditors for Due Diligence.
* Merger or Acquisition Partners. We may share your Personal Information with third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our organization or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other organizations or merge with them. If a change happens to our organization, then the new owners may use your Personal Information in the same way as set out in this privacy policy.
* With other third parties, as required for legal compliance, law enforcement, public safety, or security purposes. For example, we may disclose your Personal Information if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or with legal process, such as to comply with a subpoena, protect and defend our rights and property, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our websites, or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. Or, for example, we may release Personal Information to comply with a court order or subpoena. Or, if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, we may release Personal Information as part of any investigation into your actions.

Privacy rights of California residents  
If you are a California resident, you have the right, under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed Personal Information for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year. Please email requests for such information to [privacy@metrocorpmedia.com](mailto:privacy@metrocorpmedia.com).

5\. Disclaimers
---------------

While _MetroCorp_ has taken reasonable steps to limit the uses of information provided by you, we cannot guarantee that the information will remain permanently secure. There is always a possibility that your information could be lost due to technical problems or stolen from our databases. _MetroCorp_ is not responsible for any such loss or theft or any other unanticipated security breach.

6\. Children’s Online Privacy
-----------------------------

Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“**COPPA**”), our Site is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13. Philadelphia does not knowingly collect personal information from children through our Site. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must obtain the permission of their parents or legal guardians before making purchases of any type.

If you are a parent with concerns about children’s privacy issues in conjunction with the use of this Site, or any other privacy issue, please contact us at [privacy@metrocorpmedia.com](mailto:privacy@metrocorpmedia.com).

7\. Data Security
-----------------

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

8\. California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights
--------------------------------------------------------

If you are a California resident, you have the right, under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed Personal Information for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year. Please email requests for such information to [privacy@metrocorpmedia.com](mailto:privacy@metrocorpmedia.com).

9\. Changes to This Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the applicable data protection and privacy laws and principles. We will post those changes on our Site so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will also notify you by email or a means of a notice on our Site prior to the changes becoming effective, if we make changes that materially affect the way we handle Personal Information.

Your continued interaction, both online and offline, after an update will indicate your acceptance. This constitutes your consent and agreement to abide by this Privacy Policy and your consent to the use of the information that we collect, including personally identifiable information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Should you not wish _MetroCorp_ to collect and use your personal information in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide the information to _MetroCorp_.

10\. Contact Information
------------------------

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, please contact us at:  
Email: [privacy@metrocorpmedia.com](mailto:privacy@metrocorpmedia.com)

Mail: PO Box 40059, Philadelphia, PA 19106

Phone: 215-564-7700

_Updates to Personal Information:_ If you would like to update the Personal Information that we have about you, or if you no longer desire our products, services, or information, please contact us at the above contact information.

_Unsubscribe Requests:_ If you would like to unsubscribe from our email lists, you can do so by using the unsubscribe link in a direct marketing email you have received.

* * *

Trending
--------

1. ### [Mayor Parker Wants Speed Cameras All Over Philadelphia](https://www.phillymag.com/news/2024/06/04/philadelphia-speed-cameras-mayor-parker/)
    
2. ### [Class Action Lawsuit Filed Against University of the Arts](https://www.phillymag.com/news/2024/06/05/university-of-the-arts-lawsuit/)
    
3. ### [Where to Get a Head Spa Treatment in and Around Philadelphia](https://www.phillymag.com/be-well-philly/head-spa-scalp-massage-philadelphia/)
    
4. ### [An Insider’s Guide to Philly’s Best Wine Bar Happy Hours](https://www.phillymag.com/foobooz/best-wine-bar-happy-hours-philadelphia/)
    
5. ### [Fishtown Seafood Opens New Spot With “Golden Oyster” Promo](https://www.phillymag.com/foobooz/2024/06/04/fishtown-seafood-fitler-square-golden-oyster/)
